Whenever, Wherever
Lucky you were born that far away so we could both make fun of distance
Lucky that
I love a foreign man for the lucky fact of your existence
Baby
I would climb the
Andes solely to count the freckles on your body
Never could imagine there were only ten million ways to love somebody
Leh roh loh leh loh leh leh loh loh leh loh leh
Can't you see
I'm at your feet
Whenever, wherever we're meant to be together
I'll be there and you'll be near and that's the deal my dear
There over, hereunder you'll never have to wonder
We can always play by ear but that's the deal my dear
Lucky that my lips not only mumble
They spill kisses like a fountain
Lucky that my breasts are small and humble so you don't confuse them with mountains
Lucky
I have strong legs like my mother to run for cover when
I need it
And these two eyes that for no other
The day you leave will cry a river
Leh roh loh leh loh leh leh roh loh leh loh leh
At your feet
I'm at your feet
Whenever,
Wherever we're meant to be together
I'll be there and you'll be near and that's the deal my dear
There over, hereunder you'll never have to wonder
We can always play by ear but that's the deal my dear
Leh roh loh leh loh leh leh roh loh leh loh leh
Think out loud say it again
Leh roh loh leh loh leh loh leh
Tell me one more time that you'll live lost in my eyes
Whenever, wherever we'll meant to be together
I'll be there and you'll be near and that's the deal my dear
There over, hereunder you've got me head over heels
There's nothing left to fear if you really feel the way
I feel
Whenever, wherever we're meant to be together
I'll be there and you'll be near and that's the deal my dear
There over, hereunder you've got me head over heels
There's nothing left to fear if you really feel the way
I feel